A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, General Correspondence FA735
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1953
  - State Department, 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Stedman, Eugene, 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Stein, Clarence, 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Stellare, Fred R., 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Stewart, Maxwell S., 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Stone, Shepard, 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Supomo, R., 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - TA - TZ [General File], 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Tax Exemptions, 1953 (Reel C-1166)
  - Taxes - Welfare Exemption - Property Taxes, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Technical Assistance, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Technical Assistance Board, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Technical Cooperation Admin., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Technical Cooperation Admin., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Thailand, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Tolley, Howard R., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - UA - UZ [General File], 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - UNESCO, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - United Nations, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - VA - VZ [General File], 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - WA - WZ [General File], 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Warfield, Benjamin B., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Williams, Douglas Associates, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Wilson, M., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Wolf, Alfred C., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Wood, Tyler, 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Wyzanski, Charles E., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - YA - YZ [General File], 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - Young, James W., 1953 (Reel C-1167)
  - ZA - ZZ [General File], 1953 (Reel C-1167)
- General Correspondence, 1954
  - AA - AZ, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Advisory Committee on International Training and Research (ACITR), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Afghanistan, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Africa, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Aikin, Charles, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American..., 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Council of Voluntary Services, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Council on Education, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Friends of the Middle East, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Home Economics Association, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Hotel Association, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American Red Cross, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - American University of Beirut, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Appleby, Paul, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Arden House Conference, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Area I (Peace), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Area II (Democracy), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Area III (Economic Development), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Area IV (Education), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Area V (Behavioral Sciences), 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Armour Research Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Arnold, Edwin, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Ascher, Charles S., 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Ashmore Project, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Asia, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Asia Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Atomic Industrial Forum, 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - BA - BZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1168)
  - Bailey, Stephen K., 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Board on Overseas Training and Research (BOTR), 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Board on Overseas Training and Research (BOTR) - recruitment program (Munford), 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Board on Overseas Training and Research (BOTR) - recruitment program (Thompson), 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Brohm, John F., 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Brown, William O., 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Burma, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - CA - CZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Caldwell, John T. (Dr.), 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Carnegie Corporation of America, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Carskadon, Thomas R., 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Center for International Studies, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Chekhov Publishing House, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - China, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Clifford, Robert L., 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Columbia University, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1954 (Reel C-1169)
  - Communism, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Conferences, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Conservation Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Council (General), 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - DA - DZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Davis, Chester, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - DeKiewiet, Cornelis, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Detroit Meeting on Metropolitan problem, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - EA - EZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Egger, Rowland, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Egypt, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Ensminger, Douglas, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Ethridge, Mark F., 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Everton, John, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Exchange of Persons, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - FA - FZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Ford, Benson, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Ford, Henry II, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Foreign Operations Administration, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Foreign Service Educational Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1170)
  - Foundations, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Fund for Adult Education, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Fund for the Advancement of Education, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - GA - GZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Gaither, H. Rowan, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Gould, Lawrence M., 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Graham, Milton, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - HA - HZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Hickey, Margaret, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Hoffman, Paul, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Holmes, Horace, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Hoskins, Harold B., 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - IA - IZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - India - Douglas Ensminger & Carl C. Taylor report, "The national development program of India with specific reference to its rural sector", 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - India, Publication on Ford Foundation Activities in, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - India, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Indonesia, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Institute of International Education, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - International Legal Studies, 1954 (Reel C-1171)
  - International Research Associates, Inc., 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - International..., 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Iraq, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Isard, Walter (Professor), 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - JA - JZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Japan, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Johnson, V. Webster, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Johnson (General), 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Juvenile Delinquency - (Staff Interviews & Reports), 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - KA - KZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - LA - LZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Langer, Paul, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Lebanon, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Lewis, Oscar Dr., 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Liberal Arts Colleges, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Lockwood, William, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - MA - MZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - McDaniel, Joseph M., 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Maris, Paul, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Miller, (General), 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - Miller, Edwin, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - NA - NZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - National Civic Service League, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - National Information Bureau, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - National Municipal League, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - National Planning Association, 1954 (Reel C-1172)
  - National Science Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - National, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Near East, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Near East Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Neill, George, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - New York State Joint Legislative Committee on Problems of Aging, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - North Carolina University, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - OA - OZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Office of Defense Mobilization, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Operations Coordinating Board, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas..., 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas - Howard and Price trip, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas Conference, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas Photographs, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas Reports, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas Staff Meetings, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - Overseas Standard Reports, 1954 (Reel C-1173)
  - PA - PZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Pakistan, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Paul, Benjamin, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Pool, Ithiel de Sola, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - RA - RZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Rabinowitz, Richard W., 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Reece Committee, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Resources for the Future, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Riecken, Henry W., 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - SA - SZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Sage, Russell Foundation, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Shaw, A. Vere, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Silberman, Leo, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Spaeth, Carl, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Stalnaker, John M., 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Syria, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - TA - TZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Taylor (General), 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Thompson (General), 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Turkey, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - United States, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - WA - WZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Washington Seminar on International Affairs, 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Webb (General), 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - YA - YZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - Young (General), 1954 (Reel C-1174)
  - ZA - ZZ [General File], 1954 (Reel C-1174)
- General Correspondence, 1955
  - AA - AZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Abrams, Frank W., 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Ackerman, Edward A., 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Adams, Arthur S., 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Africa, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Advisory Committee on International Training & Research (ACITR), 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Advisory Committee on International Training & Research (ACITR) - Dockets, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Agriculture, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Allen, H. B., 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Alexander, Robert, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - American Institute of Public Opinion, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - American Library Association, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - American Political Science Association, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - American Red Cross, 1955 (Reel C-1175)
  - Area I (Peace) - Reports, 1955 (Reel C-1175, Reel C-1176)
  - Area II (Democracy), 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Area III (Economic Development), 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Area V (Behavioral Sciences), 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - American A-Z, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Associated..., 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Asia Foundation, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Asian Centers and Surveys, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Association..., 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - BA - BZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Bowen, Howard R., 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Bowles, Chester, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Brownler, James F., 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Burma, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Hsin Hua Yueh Pao (New China Monthly Gazette), 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Howell, Ernest, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - House of Representatives (U.S.), 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Holmes, Horace, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Hill, Rey M., 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Harvard University, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - Harris, Michael, 1955 (Reel C-1176)
  - CA - CZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - California, University of, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Carnegie...., 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - China, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Citizens..., 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Cleveland, Harlan, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Columbia University, Dept. of Chinese + Japanese Studies, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Cornell University, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Costello, William, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Council..., 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Cowles, John, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - DA - DZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - David, Donald K., 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Detroit Meeting on Metropolitan Problem, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Dharmawara, Vira, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - EA - EZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Eggan, Fred, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Egypt, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ensminger, Douglas, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ethridge, Mark, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Everton, John Scott, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Exchange of Persons, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - FA - FZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Fisher, Harold, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ford, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ford, Benson, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ford, Henry II, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ford Motor Company, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Ford Stock, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Foreign, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Fortune Magazine, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Fox, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - France, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Fund for Asia, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Fund for the Republic, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - GA - GZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Gaither, H. Rowan, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Gant, George, 1955 (Reel C-1177)
  - Garceau, Oliver, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gardner, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gideonse, Harry D., 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Goormaghtigh, John, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gordon, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gould, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gould, Laurence M. (Dr.), 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Graham, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Grand, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Graves, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gray, Gordon, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gross, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Gustavson, Reuben G., 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - HA - HZ, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
    See also reel C-1176 for 1955 H General Correspondence file
  - Harris, Michael, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Harvard University, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Hill, Rey M., 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Holmes, Horace, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - House of Representatives (U.S.), 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Howell, Ernest M., 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Hsin Hua Yueh Pao (New China Monthly Gazette), 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - IA - IZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - India, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - India - Publication on Ford Foundation Activities, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Indonesia, 1955 (Reel C-1178)
  - Institute..... [General], 1955 (Reel C-1179)
  - Institute of International Education, 1955 (Reel C-1179)
  - International ... [General], 1955 (Reel C-1179)
  - Inter-American Investment-Conference, 1955 (Reel C-1179)
  - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1955 (Reel C-1179)
  - International Cooperation Administration, 1955 (Reel C-1179)
  - International Educational Exchange Service (U.S. State Department), 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - International Legal Studies, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Iran, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Iraq, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - JA - JZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Japan, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Johnson..., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Johnstone, William G., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Jones...., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Jordan, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Juvenile Delinquency, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - KA - KZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Katz, Milton, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Kellogg Foundation, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - LA - LZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Lebanon, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Lincoln, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Little, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Los Angeles, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Louisiana Raulerson Hospital, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Low, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - MA - MZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - McClelland, David C., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - McCloy, John J., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - McDaniel, Joseph M. Jr., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Michigan, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Miller... (Surname), 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Missouri..., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Mitchell..., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Mount (Mt.), 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - Murrow, Edward R., 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - NA - NZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - National (General), 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - National Book Committee, 1955 (Reel C-1180)
  - National Education Association of the United States, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - National Information Bureau, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - National Planning Association, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - National Science Foundation, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - National Workshop on World Economic and Social Development, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Near East, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Near East Foundation, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Nepal, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - New..., 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - New York University, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Newman..., 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - OA - OZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Office of Education, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Ohio State University, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Operations Coordinating Board, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Operations Mission to the Philippines, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Operations Missions, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Overseas Training and Research (OTR), 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Overseas Training and Research (OTR) Fellowships, 1955 January - June (Reel C-1181)
  - Overseas Training and Research (OTR) - Status Report, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Overseas... (General), 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Overseas Photographs, 1955 (Reel C-1181)
  - Overseas Development Program Status Report, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Overseas Representatives Conference, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - PA - PZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Pakistan, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Public..., 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Public Administration Clearing House, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - RA - RZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Rand Corporation, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Reece Committee, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Resources for the Future, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Rice..., 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Rockefeller..., 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - SA - SZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Sage, Russell Foundation, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Saudi Arabia, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Schneider, David M., 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Schramm, Wilbur, 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Sisters of...., 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Smith... (General), 1955 (Reel C-1182)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Spaeth, Carl B., 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Senate Committee on Foreign Relations, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Stanford Research Institute, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Stanford University, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - State Department (U.S.), 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Stone..., 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Syracuse University, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Syria, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - TA - TZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Taylor, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Technical Assistance Administration, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Temporary Commission on the Courts, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Thailand, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Thompson... (General), 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Trinity..., 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Truman, David B., 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - Turkey, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - UNESCO, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - UNESCO Conference of Chiefs of Mission, Djakarta, Indonesia, 1955 August 29 - September 2 (Reel C-1183)
  - University..., 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - United States Council of the International Chamber of Commerce, Inc., 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - United States Information Agency, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - United States National Commission on UNESCO, 1955 (Reel C-1183)
  - VA - VZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Vanderbilt, 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - WA - WZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Washington Seminar on International Affairs, 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Wilson, Robert E., 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - World..., 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Wright..., 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Wyzanski, Charles E. Jr., 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - YA - YZ [General File], 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Yale University, 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Young, 1955 (Reel C-1184)
  - Yugoslavia, 1955 (Reel C-1184)
- General Correspondence, 1956
  - AA - AZ [General File], 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Abramovitz, Moses, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Abrams, Frank W., 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Advisory Committee on International Training and Research (ACITR), 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Africa, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Agriculture, U.S. Dept. of, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Agricultural Missions Inc., 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Air..., 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Alexander..., 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - Allott, Gordon, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American... (A-Z General), 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Academy, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Assembly, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Association..., 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Association of Land Grant Colleges and State Universities, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Bar Association, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American College Public Relations Association, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Committee..., 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Council on Education, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Hospital Association, 1956 (Reel C-1185)
  - American Institute of Public Opinion, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - American Legion..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - American Management Association, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - American Red Cross, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Anderson..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Anderson, Robert B., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Andrews..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Area I (Peace), 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Area II (Democracy), 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Area III (Economic Development), 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Area IV (Education), 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Area V (Behavioral Sciences), 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Arizona Hospital Association, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Army..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Arnold, Edwin G., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Asia, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Asia Foundation, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Association... (A - Z General), 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Association for Applied Solar Energy, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Association for Higher Education, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Atlanta..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Atlantic..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Atomic..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - BA - BZ [General File], 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Bacon, G.H., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Baldwin-Wallace College, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Baltimore Council of Social Agencies, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Baptist..., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Bard, Erwin, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Barker, Joseph, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Bates, Charles R., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Baylor University, 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Beardsley, Richard K., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Beckman, George M., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Bell, Howard M., 1956 (Reel C-1186)
  - Benjamin, Edward, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Benner, Thomas, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bennett, John, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Berman, Harold, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Birmingham..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Black, James B., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bloomfield, Lincoln P., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Blue..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Board of Pensions of the Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bologna Center School of Advanced International Studies, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bond..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Booth..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Boots and Saddles, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bose, Aurobindo, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Boston Chamber of Commerce, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Boston..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bowen, Howard, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bowers, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bowles, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Brady, Leslie, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Branford Electric Railway Association, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Breyn, Sylvan, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - British Sociological Association, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Brookings Institution, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Brooklyn College, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Brooks..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Brown, Dyke, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Brown... (General), 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bryan... (General), 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Burke..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Buck..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Buckingham, Richard, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Budiadjo, Ali, 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Buffalo..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Bureau..., 1956 (Reel C-1187)
  - Burma, 1956 (Reel C-1187, Reel C-1188)
  - Burness, Carl G., 1956 (Reel C-1188)
  - Burns..., 1956 (Reel C-1188)
  - Burt..., 1956 (Reel C-1188)
  - Byelorussian Orthodox Church, 1956 (Reel C-1188)
  - CA - CZ [General File], 1956 (Reel C-1188)
  - Caldwell, 1956 (Reel C-1188)